putumayo.com 2017-02-25

# Privacy Policy | Putumayo World Music

**Putumayo Email Policy**  
If you subscribe to our email list, the email address you provide will be sent e-mails pertaining to Putumayo-only promotional offers, cultural and company news, new release information and order processing confirmations. We will not send you advertisements from third parties. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include a simple unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

**Putumayo Online Account Policy**  
We use the account information you provide to fulfill orders and assist with customer service only. Your account information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company.

**Your information is safe**  
Putumayo is an Authorize.net verified merchant and uses industry standard 128-bit SSL encryption to keep your information safe. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable outside information to outside parties. 

We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via filling in a form on our website.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Analytics Tools  
** This website uses various web analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) and other measurement tools to help analyze how users use the site. These tools use ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form.  
We will never use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site.

If you want to disable the use of Google Analytics for your browser then you can use the following browser extension:  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

**Disabling & Enabling Cookies  
**You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings on your browser.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. The policy was last modified 02/22/2017.
